laptoppricelist.in 2019-06-10

# 

## Privacy Policy:

It is **http://www.laptoppricelist.in**  (the “Site”) policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, http://www.laptoppricelist.in collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. laptoppricelist.in’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how laptoppricelist.in’s visitors use its website. From time to time, laptoppricelist.in may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

laptoppricelist.in also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on laptoppricelist.in blogs/sites. laptoppricelist.in only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to laptoppricelist.in website choose to interact with laptoppricelist.in in ways that require laptoppricelist.in to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that laptoppricelist.in gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at laptoppricelist.in to provide a username and email address. laptoppricelist.in collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with laptoppricelist.in. laptoppricelist.in does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

laptoppricelist.in may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. laptoppricelist.in may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, laptoppricelist.in does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

laptoppricelist.in discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on laptoppricelist.in behalf or to provide services available at laptoppricelist.in websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using laptoppricelist.in websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. laptoppricelist.in will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, laptoppricelist.in discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when laptoppricelist.in believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of laptoppricelist.in, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an laptoppricelist.in website and have supplied your email address, laptoppricelist.in may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with laptoppricelist.in and our products. If you send us a request (for example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. laptoppricelist.in takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. laptoppricelist.in uses cookies to help laptoppricelist.in identify and track visitors, their usage of laptoppricelist.in website, and their website access preferences. laptoppricelist.in visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using laptoppricelist.in websites, with the drawback that certain features of laptoppricelist.in websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Business Transfers

If laptoppricelist.in, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that laptoppricelist.in goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of laptoppricelist.in may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by laptoppricelist.in and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, laptoppricelist.in may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in laptoppricelist.in’s sole discretion. laptoppricelist.in encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a laptoppricelist.in account, you might also receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

**Your Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html> Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, http://www.LaptopPriceList.in has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers. You may at anytime opt out of cookies by visiting those websites (if the vendor or ad network offers this capability). You can opt out of some, but not all, of these cookies in one location at the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out website at [www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**Collection of Personal Information**  
When visiting http://www.LaptopPriceList.in, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Links to third party Websites**  
We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of http://www.LaptopPriceList.in then you may contact us at **laptoppriceindia@gmail.com**
